Renaissance Architecture Lantern Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Spain (Box 122)
  - Palma del Condado (Box 127)
  - Pamplona (Box 127)
  - Penaranda de Dueto (Box 127)
  - Plascencia (Box 127)
  - Ronda (Box 127)
  - Salamanca (Box 127–128)
    - Churches (Box 128)
    - Schools (Box 128)
      - Various (Box 128)
      - Escuelas Menores (Box 128)
      - University (Box 128)
  - Saldanuela (Box 128)
  - Sanguesa (Box 128)
  - Santa Maria Del Campo (Box 128)
  - Santiago de Compostella (Box 128)
    - S. Martin Pinario (Box 128)
    - Royal Hospital (Box 128)
  - Segovia (Box 128)
  - Seville (Box 128)
    - Churches (Box 128)
      - Cathedral (Box 128–129)
        - S. Luis (Box 129)
      - Government Buildings (Box 129)
        - Ayuntamiento (City Hall) (Box 129)
        - Exchange (Box 129)
        - Hospitals (Box 129)
        - Industrial Buildings (Box 129)
          - Tobacco Factory (Box 129)
        - Palaces (Box 129)
          - Alcazar (Box 129)
          - Archbishop's Palace (Box 129)
  - Siguenza (Box 129)
  - Sobrado de los Monjes (Box 129)
  - Tarragona (Box 129)
  - Toledo (Box 129)
    - Churches (Box 129)
      - Cathedral (Box 129)
    - Government Buildings (Box 129)
      - Alcazar (Box 129)
      - Ayuntamiento (Box 129)
    - Hospitals (Box 129)
      - Hospital of S. Cruz (Box 129)
      - S. Juan Bautista (Box 129–130)
  - Trujillo (Box 130)
  - Ubeda (Box 130)
    - Church (Box 130)
    - Palace (Box 130)
  - Ucles (Box 130)
  - Valencia (Box 130)
  - Valladolid (Box 130)
    - Cathedral (Box 130)
  - Viana, Navarra (Box 130)
  - Vich (Box 130)
  - Villagarcia de Campos (Box 130)
  - Villarreal (Box 130)
  - Zaragoza (Box 130)
    - Various (Box 130)
    - Virgen del Pilar (Box 130)
    - S. Cajetan (Box 130)
- Sweden (Box 130–131)
  - Various (Box 131)
- Switzerland (Box 131)
  - Various (Box 131)
  - Basel (Box 131)
  - St. Gall (Box 131)
  - Vevey (Box 131)
  - Zurich (Box 131)
- Yugoslavia (Box 131)
  - Various (Box 131)
  - Dubrovinik (Box 131)
- Latin America (Box 131)
  - Argentina (Box 131)
    - Cordoba (Box 131)
    - Corrientes (Box 131)
    - Purmamarca (Box 131)
    - Salta (Box 131)
    - Santa Fe (Box 131)
  - Bolivia (Box 131)
    - Copacabana (Box 131)
    - Potosi (Box 132)
    - Sucre (Box 132)
  - Brazil (Box 132)
    - Cattas Altas (Box 132)
    - Congonhas do Campo (Box 132)
    - Mariana (Box 132)
    - Ouro Preto (Box 132)
    - Rio de Janeiro (Box 132)
    - Salvador (Box 132)
    - S. Joao del Rei (Box 132)
  - Colombia (Box 132)
    - Manizales (Box 132)
  - Cuba (Box 132)
    - Havana (Box 132)
  - Dominican Republic (Box 132)
    - Santo Domingo (Box 132)
  - Ecuador (Box 132)
    - Quito (Box 132)
  - Guatemala (Box 132)
    - Various (Box 132)
  - Mexico (Box 133)
    - General (Box 133)
    - Acapulco (Box 133)
    - Acatepec (Box 133)
      - S. Francisco (Box 133)
    - Acatzingo (Box 133)
    - Acolman (Box 133)
    - Actopan (Box 133)
    - Aguas Calientes (Box 133)
    - Apam (Box 133)
    - Atlatlauhcan (Box 133)
    - Atlihuetzia (Box 133)
    - Atlixco (Box 133)
    - Calkini (Box 133)
    - Calpan (Box 133)
    - Campeche (Box 133)
    - Chicuolopa (Box 133)
    - Chihuahua (Box 133)
    - Cholula (Box 133)
      - Royal Chapel (Box 133)
    - Coatepec (Box 133)
    - Conkal (Box 133)
    - Coyoacan (Box 133)
    - Ciudad Hidalgo (Box 133)
    - Cuernavaca (Box 133)
    - Cuilapan (Oaxaca) (Box 133)
    - Cuitzeo (Box 133)
    - Culhuacan (Box 133)
    - Dzemul (Box 133)
    - Dzidzantun (Box 134)
    - Epazoyucan (Box 134)
    - Etla (Box 134)
    - Guadalajara (Box 134)
    - Guadalupe (Box 134)
    - Guanajuato (Box 134)
    - Hacienda de Arcos (Box 134)
    - Hacienda de San Antonio Xala (Box 134)
    - Hacienda de San Lorenzo (Box 134)
    - Hacienda of San Miguel Mimihuapan (Box 134)
    - Hacienda de Santiago Tetlapaya (Box 134)
    - Hacienda de Tecajete (Box 134)
    - Halacho (Box 134)
    - Hocaba (Box 134)
    - Huejotzingo (Box 134)
    - Huexutla de Hidalgo (Box 134)
    - Hunucma (Box 134)
    - Ixmiquilpan (Box 134)
    - Izamal (Box 134)
    - Mama, Yucatan (Box 134)
    - Malinalco (Box 134)
    - Mani (Box 134)
    - Merida (Box 134)
      - Churches (Box 134)
        - Las Monjas (Box 134)
        - La Mejorada (Box 134)
        - S. Cristobal (Box 134)
        - Cathedral of San Ildefonso (Box 134–135)
        - S. Bautista (Box 135)
        - S. Juan De Dios (Box 135)
        - S. Sebastian (Box 135)
        - Church of Santiago (Box 135)
        - Tercera Orden (Box 135)
      - Gates (Box 135)
      - Governements Buildings (Box 135)
      - Houses & Palaces (Box 135)
        - Casa de Montejo (Box 135)
    - Metztitlan (Box 135)
    - Mexico City (Box 135)
      - Banks (Box 135)
      - Churches (Box 135)
        - Cathedral (Box 135)
          - Exterior (Box 135–136)
          - Interior (Box 136)
        - La Ensenanza (Box 136)
        - La Merced (Box 136)
        - Oratoria of S. Felipo Neri (Box 136)
        - La Profesa (Box 136)
        - Regina Coeli (Box 136)
        - Sagrario (Box 136)
          - Exterior (Box 136)
          - Exterior details (Box 136)
          - Interior (Box 136)
        - Salto del Agua (Box 136)
        - Santa Veracruz (Box 136)
        - Santisima Trinidad (Box 136)
        - St. Augustine (Box 136)
        - S. Domingo (Box 136)
        - S. Fernando (Box 136)
        - S. Francisco (Box 136)
        - S. Jose de los Naturales (Box 136)
        - S. Juan de Dios (Box 136)
      - Government Buildings (Box 136)
        - Ayuntamiento (Box 136)
        - National Palace (Box 136)
      - Houses (Box 136)
        - Casa de los Condes de Jaral de Berrio (Box 136)
        - Casa de los Condes de Santiago Calimaya (Box 136)
        - House of Tiles (Box 136)
      - Hotels (Box 136)
        - Hotel Iturbide (Box 136)
      - Fountains (Box 136)
      - Parks (Box 136)
      - Schools (Box 136)
        - Las Vizcainas (Box 136)
      - Squares (Box 136)
        - Zocalo (Plaza Mayor) (Box 136)
    - Molango (Box 137)
    - Molango (Box 137)
    - Monterey (Box 137)
    - Morelia (Box 137)
    - Muna (Box 137)
    - Nochiztlan (Box 137)
    - Oaxaca (Box 137)
      - Chapel of the Rosary (Box 137)
      - La Soledad (Box 137)
      - S. Domingo (Box 137)
    - Ocuituco (Box 137)
    - Oxkutecah (Box 137)
    - Patzcuaro (Box 137)
    - Puebla (Box 137)
      - Churches (Box 137)
        - Cathedral (Box 137)
        - S. Domingo (Box 137)
        - S. Francisco (Box 137)
        - S. Jose (Box 137)
      - Houses (Box 137)
        - Casa de Alfenique (Box 137)
    - Queretaro (Box 137)
      - Churches (Box 137)
        - Convent of S. Augustin (Box 137)
        - Convent of S. Rosa de Viterbo (Box 137)
    - Quintana Roo (Box 137)
    - Regina (Box 137)
    - Saltillo (Box 137)
    - San Angel (Box 137)
    - San Cristobal las Casas (Box 137)
      - Nuestra Senora del Carmen (Box 137)
      - S. Agustin (Box 137)
      - S. Francisco (Box 137)
    - Santa Elena (Box 137)
    - Tacuba (Box 137)
    - Taxco (Box 137)
      - S. Sebastian & Prisca (Box 137–138)
    - Tecali (Box 138)
    - Tecamalchalco (Box 138)
    - Tecoh (Box 138)
    - Tekanto (Box 138)
    - Tekax, Yucatan (Box 138)
    - Tepeaca (Box 138)
    - Tepeapulco (Box 138)
    - Tepeji Del Rio (Box 138)
    - Teposcolula (Box 138)
    - Tepotzotlan (Box 138)
    - Tepoztlan, Morelos (Box 138)
    - Teutenanco (Box 138)
    - Texupa (Box 138)
    - Ticul (Box 138)
    - Tlacolula (Box 138)
    - Tlahuelilpa (Box 138)
    - Tlalmanalco (Box 138)
    - Tlalnepantla (Box 138)
    - Tlanaco (Box 138)
    - Tlatelolco (Box 138)
    - Tlaxcala (Box 138–139)
    - Tonanzintla (Box 139)
    - Totolinga (Box 139)
    - Tula (Box 139)
    - Tzicatlan (Box 139)
    - Uruapan (Box 139)
    - Valladolid (Box 139)
    - Veracruz (Box 139)
    - Xochimilco (Box 139)
    - Yanhuitlan (Box 139)
    - Yecapixtla (Box 139)
    - Yururia (Box 139)
    - Zacapu (Box 139)
    - Zacatecas (Box 139)
    - Zacatlan (Box 139)
    - Zempoala (Box 139)
    - Zimapan (Box 139)
  - Panama (Box 139)
  - Paraguary (Box 139)
  - Peru (Box 139)
    - Arequipa (Box 139)
    - Cajamarca (Box 140)
    - Cuzco (Box 140)
    - Juli (Box 140)
    - Lima (Box 140)
      - Churches (Box 140)
        - Cathedral (Box 140)
        - La Merced (Box 140)
        - S. Augustin (Box 140)
        - S. Francisco (Box 141)
      - Hospitals (Box 141)
    - Puno (Box 141)
    - Pupuja (Box 141)
    - Sana (Box 141)
    - Yanahuara (Box 141)
  - Venezuela (Box 141)
    - Caracas (Box 141)